sparkinfosys.com 2014-12-07

# Spark Infosys - Privacy Policy | Web Designing and Web Development

## Privacy Policy

By using our website you agree to use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change terms of this Privacy Policy at any time without any prior notice. Any changes will be inserted on this page and visitors to the web site should check this page often. Your continued use of the site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

## Information Collected Automatically

In some cases, we may collect technical information when you connect to our site that is not personal information. For example, operating system used, browser used, URL of referred site from which you accessed our site etc Furthermore, when you view our site, some information may be stored on your computer. This information will be in the form of a cookie or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the site to better match your interests and preferences. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

## Privacy Information

We will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or email address) through our site unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you.

When you do provide us with personally identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise:

  * We may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services;
  * We may contact you regarding promotions and other offers regarding our products that may interest you.

We do not now, and do not intend to, sell, rent or market personally identifiable information about you to third parties. We share information only with subsidiaries of this site and may use it to send you promotions and product information.
